They're giving dirty rotten men a run for their money.
The Hustle is a comedy, crime film directed by Chris Addison.
Two female scam artists, one low rent and the other high class,
compete to swindle a naïve tech prodigy out of his fortune.
A remake of the 1988 comedy "Dirty Rotten Scoundrels."
Penny Rust, played by Rebel Wilson.
Josephine Chesterfield, played by Anne Hathaway.
Investor, played by Kumud Pant.
Thomas Westerburg, played by Alex Sharp.
Brigitte Desjardins, played by Ingrid Oliver.
Shiraz, played by Hannah Waddingham.
The Hustle is a 2019 American comedy film directed by Chris Addison,
starring  Anne Hathaway, Rebel Wilson and Alex Sharp.
It was written by Stanley Shapiro, Paul Henning, Dale Launer, and Jac Schaeffer.
It is a female-led remake of the 1988 film Dirty Rotten Scoundrels,
which is a remake of the 1964 film Bedtime Story.
The film follows two women who set out to con an Internet millionaire.
The film was theatrically released in the United States on May 10, 2019, by United
Artists Releasing, and internationally distributed by Universal Pictures.
It received negative reviews from critics and grossed $97 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of bet, competition, affectation, con artist, swindler.
The tone is lighthearted.